[{"answer": "Well, they go from Brighton to Summerville to Cambridge looking for gasoline because apparently there was this plan cooked up to go to New York City and the tank only had about a quarter full.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "At what stage does he get away from them?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What was his account of that?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "This is entitled to a complete independent investigation, as opposed to any kind of partisan charges back and forth, because this is very, very serious, that we didn't identify this man properly is something that we shouldn't allow to happen in the future.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "I would think so.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Is that where you think the secret of all this really lies?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "As Senator Graham said, America needs to step up its game.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "What can Americans do to secure itself?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "We were on Boylston Street, not far from the finish line, and after looking at the photos that I've seen from that day, we were probably only three or four feet from where the first bomb went off.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Where were you when these bombs went off?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, after the first bomb went off, we were knocked to the ground and my first reaction I guess maybe I watch too much TV, my first reaction was to climb on top of Kaitlynn and I was yelling at her to stay down.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "And what was your instant reaction after they had gone off?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "It was the first blast.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Was it the first or second blast you think that caused her injuries?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I don't know that nobody at the hospital was aware, but when we pulled up, you know, I came sort of speeding into the area outside of the emergency room and we told those people outside the door, the ambassadors that helped get us into emergency, that a bomb had gone off and we told the people that we first came in contact with in the emergency room that she was injured in the bombing and they had no idea.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "You were so fast in the action that you took that actually the doctors at the hospital were not even aware there had been a major incident, is that right?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, actually I wasn't running when they went off.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "What was the first thing that you did?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, it was.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "When you got to the hospital and you saw the kind of injuries coming in, was this reminiscent to you of a battle zone?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "So I have to -- I have to correct Leo in only the nicest way, of course.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Did you actually have anything to do with Kaitlynn at all during her time there?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "There is -- there is no doubt that the time -- the time from injury to surgical intervention, particularly for bleeding wounds, is a key factor in preventing greater disability, loss of limb and loss of life.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "In terms of the speed with which Leo managed to get Kaitlynn to the hospital, would that have played a significant effect perhaps on saving her leg if not her life?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, you know, to the room, there were some other victims and their families and friends there and to the room, he delivered what was a very inspirational speech, if you will, about seeing people who were victims of these type of injuries at Walter Reed in his visits there, and in monitoring their recovery and seeing them all, you know, recover fully or get better.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What did he have to say to you?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "She's doing better.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Finally, L, how is Kaitlynn doing?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I just missed the bombs.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Did you hear them live or were you watching somewhere?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "You know, it's about when I was there in Boston, you know, after the tragedy happened, you saw how the community came together.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What made you do it?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "You know, what went through my mind is it could have been anybody.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "When you heard that these two bomb suspects were ethnic Chechens, went what went through mind?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I'm feeling confident.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Are you feeling confident?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "There's been so much to digest, so much to comprehend of the themselves, not even thinking about the photography.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What is your reflective thought on the last fortnight?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I think it put a face on this -- it put a face on news bombings.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "The fact that people could actually see the horror, firsthand?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "There's a photo that I keep looking back at and it's a picture of a Marine.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "And of all of the images you took, so many powerful images, which of the ones stand out for you in your mind?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I went to the memorial site and I saw the three crosses there for the three victims.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "And, John, you left something at the memorial site, I believe?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Yes!", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "You guys ready?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "It's yours.", "docId": "130426pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Did you just find a basketball?", "qSentId": 485}]